{
    "id": "11f599128ded42d28dc07361bc35421b",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Our affection ………………. our children often makes us blind ………………… their defects.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of, of",
                "of, to",
                "for, to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6cc25806335c4664a0014056f201a286"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has a passion ……………… books. He is not interested ………………. anything else.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with, in",
                "for, in",
                "for, with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5a45c545db9f49c2b4409a5a7b01b9b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "The injection gave the patient relief …………………. pain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "from",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5bbb5ae3aa9f482aa425491bec13332a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We should not spend ……………….. unnecessary things.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e37ba0197ea6475e85779d85216c5685"
        },
        {
            "question": "The officer is popular ………………… his staff, because they have easy access …………….. him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with, at",
                "with, to",
                "for, to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "04c9484a51274fe588706389dc8d12b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The members objected ………………….. the offensive remarks made by the chairman.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6651b0cf47374d77838d76686e1f9f89"
        },
        {
            "question": "The examinations are likely to be postponed ………………… May.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "747d93545a7b436ea00cbe20ab4ec8a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The shirting I bought ……………. Bombay is superior ………………….. the one I bought ……………… Madras.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from, to, from",
                "from, than, from",
                "in, to, in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f74701a14baf43199eb128a7e579d2f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have succeeded …………………. making my friend give up smoking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "in",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ad06362435e54bdca42526fa0cb50e48"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have invited the District Collector to preside ………………. the meeting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "153e5c33acd04aca9cdf8055fdf7e69f"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is often very difficult to deal ……………......… unruly children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d315c3e80ba4377909906f6b91bb0b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We should sympathize ………………. those ………………….. distress.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with, in",
                "with, on",
                "for, in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "33b01e7844dd403d9f40eb48c98e8ca1"
        }
    ]
}